[
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What is Harry's middle name?",
        "answer": "James"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What color are Dobby's eyes?",
        "answer": "Green"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "Who was the headmaster of Hogwarts before Dumbledore?",
        "answer": "Armando Dippet"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What are the initials inscribed in fake horcrux locket?",
        "answer": "R.A.B."
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What spell does Lockhart use to wipe memories?",
        "answer": "Obliviate"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What color is the dragon that Fleur faces in the Triwizard Tournament?",
        "answer": "Green"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "How many real prophecies does Trelawney make in her lifetime?",
        "answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What is the name of the company that Vernon Dursley works for and what do they sell?",
        "answer": "Grunnings and they sell drills"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What amphibian comes in chocolate form and has about one good jump in it?",
        "answer": "Frog"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "How many real prophecies does Trelawney make in her lifetime?",
        "answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What does Dumbledore find in the Room of Requirement?",
        "answer": "Chamber pots"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "Who is Peeves?",
        "answer": "A poltergeist/Hogwarts poltergeist"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What is Tom Riddle's mother's maiden name?",
        "answer": "Gaunt"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What is the name of Dumbledore's phoenix?",
        "answer": "Fawkes"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "How much money do the Weasleys win in the Daily Prophet Galleon Giveaway?",
        "answer": "700"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What does O.W.L stand for?",
        "answer": "Ordinary Wizarding Level"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What famous dark wizard did Dumbledore defeat?",
        "answer": "Grindelwald"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What is the symbol of the Slytherin house?",
        "answer": "A snake"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "At what famous location does the Night Bus drop Harry off at?",
        "answer": "The Leaky Cauldron"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "Which of the Weasleys is a prefect when Harry first goes to Hogwarts?",
        "answer": "Percy"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What is the symbol of the Gryffindor house?",
        "answer": "A lion"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What is the symbole of the Hufflepuff house?",
        "answer": "A badger"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What is the symbol of the Ravenclaw house?",
        "answer": "An eagle"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "How many sickles are in a galleon?",
        "answer": "17"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "How many knuts are in a sickle?",
        "answer": "29"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "Who received a special award at Hogwarts 50 years before Harry attended?",
        "answer": "Tom Riddle"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "How many times was Nearly Headless Nick hit in the neck with a blunt axe?",
        "answer": "45 times"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What is the make and model of Mr. Weasley's flying car?",
        "answer": "Ford Anglia"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "How many brothers does Ron have?",
        "answer": "5"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "In what vault is the Sorcerors Stone kept?",
        "answer": "713"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "Who invented the headless hat?",
        "answer": "Fred and George Weasley"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What is Voldemort's father's name?",
        "answer": "Tom Riddle"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "Who is Ginny Weasley's first boyfriend?",
        "answer": "Michael Corner"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "How many galleons doe Fred and George bet on the World Cup?",
        "answer": "37"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "How many chocolate frog cards does Ron estimate he has?",
        "answer": "500"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What does Ron use to destroy Helga Hufflepuff's cup?",
        "answer": "Basilisk fang"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "How many goal posts are there in Quidditch (both sides together)?",
        "answer": "6"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What day and month is Harry's birthday?",
        "answer": "July 31st"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What is the next name in this sequence: Wormtail, Moony, Padfoot, and ____?",
        "answer": "Prongs"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "How did Harry's parents die according to the Dursley's?",
        "answer": "A car crash"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What is the Durley's address?",
        "answer": "Number 4 Privet Drive"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "How many points is catching the snitch worth?",
        "answer": "150"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "How many points is scoring the Quaffle worth?",
        "answer": "10"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What town do the Dursley's live in?",
        "answer": "Little Whinging"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What is the name of Hermione's cat?",
        "answer": "Crookshanks"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "Who is the eldest Weasley sibling?",
        "answer": "Bill or William"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "Who is the youngest Weasley sibling?",
        "answer": "Ginny"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "Who is the leader of Dumbledore's Army?",
        "answer": "Harry"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What is the name of the headquarters of the Order of the Phoenix?",
        "answer": "Grimmauld Place"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "How much does a 12 week course on apparition cost?",
        "answer": "12 galleons"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "Who replaces Fudge as Minister of Magic?",
        "answer": "Rufus Scrimgeour"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "Who is the headmaster of Durmstrang?",
        "answer": "Igor Karkaroff"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "Who is the headmistress of Beauxbatons academy?",
        "answer": "Madame Maxime"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What is the incantation for the killing curse?",
        "answer": "Avada kedavra"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What is the incantation for the levitating charm?",
        "answer": "Wingardium leviosa"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What is the name of the group of Voldemort's followers?",
        "answer": "Death Eaters"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "How do the students of Durmstrang arrive at Hogwarts?",
        "answer": "By a ship"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What spell opens the secret passage to Hogmeade behind the status of the one-eyed witch?",
        "answer": "Dissendium"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What subject is taught by Professor Binns?",
        "answer": "History of Magic"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "Who was the first student to be separated by the Sorting Hat during Harry's first year?",
        "answer": "Lavender Brown"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "How many staircases does Hogwarts have?",
        "answer": "142"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "Which animals sit on the pillars of the gates at Hogwarts?",
        "answer": "Winged boars"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What is the tallest tower at Hogwarts?",
        "answer": "The astronomy tower"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What does Professor Flitwick use to decorate his classroom for Christmas?",
        "answer": "Live fairies"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What prevents boys from entering the girl's dormitory in the Gryffindor tower?",
        "answer": "The staircase turns into a slide"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What spell turns boggarts into something humorous?",
        "answer": "Riddikulus"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What is the incantation for the summoning charm?",
        "answer": "Accio"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What spell does Harry use to try to fill the basin when Dumbledore needs a drink?",
        "answer": "Aguamenti"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What spell is used to open locked doors?",
        "answer": "Alohomora"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What is the act of disappearing from one place and reappiring in another called?",
        "answer": "Apparition"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What number in the series is Harry Potter and the Sorceror's Stone?",
        "answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What number in the series is Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets?",
        "answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What number in the series is Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban?",
        "answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What number in the series is Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire?",
        "answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What number in the series is Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix?",
        "answer": "5"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What number in the series is Harry Potter and the Half Blood Prince?",
        "answer": "6"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What number in the series is Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows?",
        "answer": "7"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What was the original name of Harry Potter and the Sorceror's Stone?",
        "answer": "Harry Potter and the Philosopher's Stone"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What does the J and K stand for in J.K. Rowling?",
        "answer": "Joanne Kathleen"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "Who killed Cedric Diggory?",
        "answer": "Wormtail/Peter Pettigrew"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What is the name of the graveyard where Voldemort was brought back to power?",
        "answer": "Little Hangleton Graveyard"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "Where did Harry's parents live when Voldemort killed them?",
        "answer": "Godrick's Hollow"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What is the name of the hippogriff that attacked Malfoy?",
        "answer": "Buckbeak"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What is the top speed of the Firebolt?",
        "answer": "150mph"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "Who sent Harry the Firebolt?",
        "answer": "Sirius Black"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What is the name of Barty Crouch's former house elf?",
        "answer": "Winky"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "In the movies, which of Mad-Eye Moody's eyes was fake?",
        "answer": "His left"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "In the books, which of Mad-Eye Moody's eyes was fake?",
        "answer": "His right"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "Who gave Harry the Cloak of Invisibility?",
        "answer": "Dumbledore"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What wood is Harry's wand made from?",
        "answer": "Holly"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What wood is Voldemort's made from?",
        "answer": "Yew"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What wood is the Elder Wand made from?",
        "answer": "Elder wood"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What pulls the Hogwarts carriages?",
        "answer": "Thestrals"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What is the core of the Elder Wand?",
        "answer": "Thestral hair"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "Which family did Dobby the free elf formerly serve?",
        "answer": "The Malfoys"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What family did Kreacher serve?",
        "answer": "The Blacks"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "Who is Dudley's childhood best friend?",
        "answer": "Piers Polkiss"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What school does Dudley go to?",
        "answer": "Smeltings"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What school do the Dursley's say that Harry goes to?",
        "answer": "St. Brutus's Secure Centre for Incurably Criminal Boys"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What frozen treat do the Dursley's buy Harry at the zoo?",
        "answer": "A cheap lemon ice pop"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What kind of snake does Harry release at the zoo?",
        "answer": "Boa constrictor"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "Where does the snake that Harry released at the zoo say it's going?",
        "answer": "Brazil"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What is the name of the Weasley's old owl?",
        "answer": "Errol"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What is the name of Percy Weasley's owl?",
        "answer": "Hermes"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What department does Arthur Weasley work in?",
        "answer": "The Misue of Muggle Artifacts"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What is the name of the Weasley's home?",
        "answer": "The Burrow"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What is Ron's mother's name?",
        "answer": "Molly Weasley"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "Who won Witch Weekly's Most Charming Smile Award five times?",
        "answer": "Gilderoy Lockhart"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "Which Order of Merlin rank is Lockhart?",
        "answer": "Third Class"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What spell backfires on Lockhart in the Chamber of Secrets?",
        "answer": "Obliviate"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What is Gilderoy Lockhart's favorite color?",
        "answer": "Lilac"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What creature did Lockhart unleash on his class?",
        "answer": "Cornish Pixies"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "At what kind of store did Harry first meet Lockhart?",
        "answer": "Book store"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "Where did Lucius Malfoy slip Ginny Weasley Tom Riddle's Diary?",
        "answer": "At Flourish and Blotts"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What is the name of Lockhart's autobiography?",
        "answer": "Magical Me"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What is the name of the institution where Lockhart resides after the Chamber of Secrets incident?",
        "answer": "St. Mungo's"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What does Hermione say is her favorite subject in Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban?",
        "answer": "Arithmancy"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What magical word extinguishes wandlight after the Lumos charm?",
        "answer": "Nox"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What is shape of Snape's patronous?",
        "answer": "A doe"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What was the profession of both of Hermione's parents?",
        "answer": "Dentist"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What foul name does Draco Malfoy call Hermione?",
        "answer": "Mudblood"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What house does the Sorting Hat consider putting Hermione into?",
        "answer": "Ravenclaw"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What is the name of the giant three-headed dog?",
        "answer": "Fluffy"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What is the name of Hagrid's pet dragon?",
        "answer": "Norbert"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What spell does Ron Weasley use to defeat the mountain troll in the girl's bathroom?",
        "answer": "Wingardium Leviosa"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "When falling down the trap door under Fluffy, what did Harry, Ron, and Hermione land on?",
        "answer": "Devil's Snare"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "How did Hermione manage to get to all of her classes in her third year?",
        "answer": "She used a Time Turner"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "Who smacked Malfoy across the face in Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban?",
        "answer": "Hermione"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What was the name of the hippogriff that attacked Draco Malfoy after he insulted the hippogriff?",
        "answer": "Buckbeak"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "Who was the only student to realize that Lupin was a werewolf when Snape assigned the essay on werewolves?",
        "answer": "Hermione"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What did Hermione use to save Sirius and Buckbeak's lives?",
        "answer": "A Time Turner"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "Who was the first house elf that Hermione met?",
        "answer": "Winky"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "Who founded S.P.E.W.?",
        "answer": "Hermione Granger"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What does S.P.E.W. stand for?",
        "answer": "Society for the Promotion of Elfish Welfare"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "How much did it cost to join S.P.E.W.?",
        "answer": "Two sickles"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What three schools participated in the Triwizard Tournament?",
        "answer": "Hogwarts, Durmstrang, and Beauxbatons"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "Who was the Bulgarian seeker?",
        "answer": "Viktor Krum"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "Who was the Durmstrang champion in the Triwizard Tournament?",
        "answer": "Viktor Krum"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "Who was the Beauxbatons champion in the Triwizard Tournament?",
        "answer": "Fleur Delacour"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What spell did Hermione help Harry learn to defeat the dragon in the first task of the Triwizard Tournament?",
        "answer": "The summoning spell (accio)"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What item did the Triwizard Tournament champions have to retrieve from the dragons?",
        "answer": "A golden egg"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "Who were the Hogwarts Triwizard Tournament champions?",
        "answer": "Harry Potter and Cedric Diggory"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "Who was Viktor Krum's date to the Yule Ball?",
        "answer": "Hermione Granger"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "Who was Fleur Delacour's date to the Yule Ball?",
        "answer": "Roger Davies"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "Who was Cedric Diggory's date to the Yule Ball?",
        "answer": "Cho Chang"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "Who did Harry first ask to accompany him to the Yule Ball?",
        "answer": "Cho Chang"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "Who was Harry's date to the Yule Ball?",
        "answer": "Parvati Patil"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "Who was Ron's date to the Yule Ball?",
        "answer": "Padma Patil"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "Who did Neville Longbottom take to the Yule Ball?",
        "answer": "Ginny Weasley"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "Who did Draco Malfoy take to the Yule Ball?",
        "answer": "Pansy Parkinson"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "Who did Fred Weasley take to the Yule Ball?",
        "answer": "Angelina Johnson"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "Who did Krum have to save from the bottom of the lake in the second task fo the Triwizard Tournament?",
        "answer": "Hermione Granger"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "Who did Harry have to save from the bottom of the lake in the second task fo the Triwizard Tournament?",
        "answer": "Ron Weasley"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "Who did Cedric have to save from the bottom of the lake in the second task fo the Triwizard Tournament",
        "answer": "Cho Chang"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "Who did Fleur have to save from the bottom of the lake in the second task fo the Triwizard Tournament",
        "answer": "Her little sister Gabrielle"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What plant does Harry use to swim in the lake during the second task in the Triwizard Tournament?",
        "answer": "Gillyweed"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "Who gives Harry the gillyweed in the book series?",
        "answer": "Dobby"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What does Viktor Krum patrially transfigure himself into during the second task in the Triwizard Tournament?",
        "answer": "A shark"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What charm does Cedric Diggory use to allow him to breathe underwater in the second task of the Triwizard Tournament?",
        "answer": "Bubblehead Charm"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "In Harry's fifth year at Hogwarts, who became the two Gryffindor prefects?",
        "answer": "Ron Weasley and Hermione Granger"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "In Harry's fifth year at Hogwarts, who became the two Slytherin prefects?",
        "answer": "Draco Malfoy and Pansy Parkinson"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What password does Cedric give Harry to get into the Prefects' Bathroom?",
        "answer": "Pine Fresh"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "Who arranged the first meeting of Dumbledore's Army?",
        "answer": "Hermione Granger"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What item did Hermione give each member of Dumbledore's Army?",
        "answer": "A coin"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "Who is the owner of the Quibbler?",
        "answer": "Xenophilius Lovegood"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "Who is the daughter of Xenophilius Lovegood?",
        "answer": "Luna Lovegood"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "Who is Arthur Weasley's coworker in the Misuse of Muggle Artifact Office?",
        "answer": "Perkins"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "In Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets, Arthur Weasley asks Harry what the function of an item is. What is the item?",
        "answer": "A rubber duck"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "In Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets, how did Harry get to Diagon Alley?",
        "answer": "He used Floo Powder"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "After first traveling by Floo Network, what street did Harry end up?",
        "answer": "Knockturn Alley"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "After first traveling by Floo Network, in what store did Harry end up?",
        "answer": "Borgin and Burkes"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "After Harry and Ron fly Arthur Weasley's car to Hogwarts, where does the car reside?",
        "answer": "The Forbidden Forest"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What color are Professor Sprout's ear muffs in Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets?",
        "answer": "Pink"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "Who do the Cornish Pixies pick up by his ears?",
        "answer": "Neville Longbottom"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What charm's incantation is immobulus?",
        "answer": "The Freezing Charm"
    },
    {
        "category": "Harry Potter",
        "question": "What detention does Harry get after he and Ron fly Arthur Weasley's car to Hogwarts?",
        "answer": "Heling Lockhart with his fan mail."
    }
]